In today's conversational world, personalized solutions on preferred channels help
businesses connect with their customers better and drive higher loyalty.
Introducing Twixer, a low-code, no-code messaging and automation platform that
accelerate your business objectives by transforming customer experience. Run personalized
campaigns, onboard customers, complete transactions, automate support services across channels
like WhatsApp, Google Business Messenger, Facebook Messenger, Instagram, Telegram or
any messaging platform. Replace old school customer service approach by
integrating our conversational AI with the latest IVR technology to
deliver instant resolution and reduce overall operational costs up to
60 percent based on understanding customer's emotion, sentiment and intent.
For instance, checking account balance, transferring funds and raising checkbook
requests, checking insurance claim status, booking health checkups, ordering groceries,
making payment and tracking deliveries, booking air tickets and checking
in. All you need to do is build templatized drag
and drop visual journeys in preferred languages. Deploy on your
customers preferred messaging channels, engage them with hyper-personalized features. With
Twixer, you can increase revenue, reduce operating costs and streamline
customer journeys. Deliver the experience your customer deserves in today's
conversational world. For large enterprises and small businesses alike, build
by technophiles across the globe.